{
    "id": "753f245306674d56914a4fd64bae0316",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… tired.",
            "description": "When feel is used to talk about reactions and opinions, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………………. amazing woman.",
            "description": "In exclamations, we use such before an adjective + plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "a such",
                "such an",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………………….. kind of you.",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. this kind of treatment from him.",
            "description": "Before an indirect object, wait and hope are followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't expect",
                "didn't hope",
                "didn't wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It seemed like he was wearing someone …………………………… coat.",
            "description": "Else has a possessive form – else’s.",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "else's",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. tired to walk.",
            "description": "Too is not used with much before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This book is an ……………………………… account of the freedom struggle.",
            "description": "Exhaustive means comprehensive or thorough.",
            "answers": [
                "exhausted",
                "exhausting",
                "exhaustive"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have difficulty ……………………………. dates and numbers.",
            "description": "Difficulty is followed by (in) + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "remembering",
                "in remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is something ……………………………..the bed.",
            "description": "We use under when something is covered by what is over it.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like this house ………………………., it is too small.",
            "description": "Besides means in addition.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t ………………………………… the car.",
            "description": "We make machines start.",
            "answers": [
                "start",
                "begin"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If my grandfather had been alive, we …………………………………… his 90th birthday in January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have celebrated",
                "would celebrate",
                "would have celebrated"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}